module Questions
  @questions = {
  question1: {question: "What is 1 + 1?", answer: "2"},
  question2: {question: "What is 2 + 2?", answer: "4"},
  question3: {question: "What is 3 + 3?", answer: "6"},
  question5: {question: "What is 5 + 5?", answer: "10"},
  question4: {question: "What is 4 + 4?", answer: "8"},
  question6: {question: "What is 6 + 6?", answer: "12"},
  question7: {question: "What is 7 + 7?", answer: "14"},
  question8: {question: "What is 8 + 8?", answer: "16"},
  question9: {question: "What is 9 + 9?", answer: "18"},
  question10: {question: "What is 10 + 10?", answer: "20"},
  question11: {question: "What is 11 + 11?", answer: "22"},
  question12: {question: "What is 12 + 12?", answer: "24"},
  question13: {question: "What is 13 + 13?", answer: "26"},
  question14: {question: "What is 14 + 14?", answer: "28"},
  question15: {question: "What is 15 + 15?", answer: "30"},
  question16: {question: "What is 16 + 16?", answer: "32"},
  question17: {question: "What is 17 + 17?", answer: "34"},
  question18: {question: "What is 18 + 18?", answer: "36"},
  question19: {question: "What is 19 + 19?", answer: "38"},
  question20: {question: "What is 20 + 20?", answer: "40"}
  }
  def self.questions
    @questions
  end
end